bridging-the-gap.com 2019-06-10

# Privacy Policy

### CLEAR SPRING BUSINESS ANALYSIS LLC

### **BY VISITING  https://bridging-the-gap.com, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY.**

#### OVERVIEW

CLEAR SPRING BUSINESS ANALYSIS LLC (“Company”) is committed to protecting your privacy online.  This Privacy Policy describes the personal data we collect through this website at https://bridging-the-gap.com (the “Site”) and what we do with it.

Visitors and any users of the site are referred to as “user”, “you” and “your” and Company is referred to as “we,” “us,” and “our.”  The Company process personal data as a Controller as defined by the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Accessing this Site constitutes a use of the Site and an acceptance to our Privacy Policy.

Use of the Site, including all materials presented herein and all online Services provided by Company, is subject to the following Privacy Policy.  This Privacy Policy applies to all site visitors, customers and all other users of the Site.  By using the Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy, without modification, and acknowledge reading it.

#### DATA WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT

This Site only collects the personal information you voluntarily provide to us, which includes your name and e-mail address, in order to subscribe to our newsletter, receive our content, comment on our blog, and/or purchase services or online products. There is also other personal data we may collect detailed herein.

We collect data from you directly when you fill out a form, purchase a product, or communicate with us via email or social media.  We also collect data from you when you use our Website.  We may collect personal data from third parties such as our payment processors, advertising networks, and/or analytics providers. Your data is stored in a secure platform.  We use your personal data for processing as outlined below or a reasonably compatible purpose.

A. _Usage Data_. We may process data about your use of our Website and services. This may include your IP address, browser type, operating system, geographical location, page views, website navigation paths, and frequency and/or pattern of your use of our website.  This data is collected through our analytics tracking systems, including Google Analytics. This data is used to analyze the use of our Website, to deliver relevant content and advertising, and understand our users. The legal basis for processing is our legitimate interest, namely monitoring and improving our website, marketing, and services.

B. _Customer Data_. We may process user data, such as name, email address, address, telephone, credit-card number, and other relevant data as related to purchases of our products and/or services. We process this data to supply products and/or services to you, as well as to market other relevant goods and services to you. The legal basis for processing is consent and your affirmative action to enter into such contract with us and/or the purchase and delivery of the contract between you and us.

C. _User Data_. We may process personal information you provide us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications, free content, and/or newsletters, as well as communication data that you send to us either through email, social media, or other posting and/or communication methods. We process this data for the purposes of communicating with you, to deliver relevant website content, and for the purposes of sending you marketing, content and/or emails. The legal basis for this process is consent or our legitimate interests, which is to grow our business and keep records which may be needed to pursue or defend a legal action.

#### MARKETING AND ADVERTISING

The above Data may be used to send you marketing communications about our business or products.  The legal basis for this type of processing is either consent or our legitimate interests in growing our business. We may send you such communications if you requested it and/or if you agreed to receive such communications. You may opt-out of such communications at any time through the ‘unsubscribe’ button in each email or contacting us at info(at)bridging-the-gap(dot)com.

Any of the above Data may be used to deliver advertisements to you, including Facebook Ads, Instagram, and/or other similar advertisements. We may also use such Data to understand the effectiveness of our advertising. The legal basis for this type of processing is our legitimate interest to grow our business through marketing and advertising.

#### SHARING YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We do share your information with trusted third parties who provide support in running this Website including any blog or newsletter, as well as those parties and services that help administer our business.  Your data will never be shared with unrelated third parties.  We may disclose your information to payment service providers, administrative and marketing providers, business advisors, or third parties if we sell or transfer parts of our Company. Third parties we share your data with will keep it secure and respect your privacy under the law and we take steps to ensure the companies we work with also comply with the GDPR.

We may record information relating to your use of the Site in order to help administer the Site and personalize your experience by improving customer service.

#### ANTI-SPAM POLICY

We comply with Anti-Spam laws. If you opt-in to receive our newsletter, marketing, or other communications, the option to unsubscribe will be included in every e-mail. If we sell or transfer any of our business or assets, certain information about our clients may be a part of that sale or transfer. In the event such sale or transfer results in a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you.

#### COOKIES

We may send cookies, Facebook pixels, and/or other tracking signals to your computer in order to uniquely identify your browser and improve the quality of our service and/or advertising. We use cookies to identify when you visit our website, to store information about your preferences, to personalize the website and/or advertisements you may see, and analyze the use and performance of our website.

The term “cookies” refers to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing the Site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). You have the ability to accept or decline cookies and tracking signals using your web browser settings. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Website may not work properly or at all.  Our Site may not respond to Do Not Track signals sent by your browser.

#### THIRD PARTY LINKS

This Site may contain links to third party websites.  Unless otherwise stated, this Privacy Policy only covers information that we collect from you on this Site. Any other link will be covered by the privacy policy of that specific site. Any other link will be covered by the privacy policy of that specific site. You acknowledge and accept that we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third parties.

#### DATA SECURITY AND BREACH RESPONSE

We do our best to protect your information for any unauthorized access, misuse, or disclosure.  We may allow access to your personal data to our employees, contractors, and service providers that need to know such data to perform necessary business services.  Personal data will be kept confidential and employees and/or contractors will only have access to it when necessary.

You acknowledge that the personal information you voluntarily share could be accessed or tampered with by a third party.  You agree that we are not responsible for any intercepted information shared through our Site without our knowledge or permission.  Additionally, you release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of such intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.  You agree to notify us for any breach of security or unauthorized use of your information.

#### DATA RETENTION AND DESTRUCTION

Personal data that we process for any purpose shall not be kept for longer than is necessary to fulfill its collection purpose or to satisfy a legal or accounting purpose.  In some cases, your data by be anonymized for research purposes and used indefinitely.  If your data no longer meets any of the above criteria, personal data will be deleted or otherwise disposed of in a safe and secure manner.

#### INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS

Your data may be transferred to other countries and by using the Website, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside your country of residence.  If you are located in the European Union, we may store and share your personal data with companies located outside of the European Economic Area.  We will always do our best to ensure security of your data.  We aim to use US-based providers that are part of the EU-US Privacy Shield.  You may always request information on how and where your data is processed and stored.

#### CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE

To access or use the Site, you must be 18 years old or older and have the requisite power and authority to enter into this Privacy Policy.  We do not knowingly collect or solicit data online from or market online to children under the age of 13 in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).

#### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

You acknowledge and agree that you have reviewed this Site and this Privacy Policy and that you will continue to review this Policy to be aware of any modifications.  We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on this Website.

#### YOUR RIGHTS

Your rights under data protection laws include the right to access, erase, correct, restrict, and/or object to our use and processing of your personal data, as well as the right to portability of the data.  You have the right to confirmation as to how and where we process your data. To the extent that the legal basis for our processing consent, you have the right to withdraw at any time. If you consider our processing to infringe data protection laws, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

#### OUR INFORMATION

This Website is owned and operated by:

Clear Spring Business Analysis LLC  
P.O. Box 4238  
Holly Ridge, NC 28445  
United States

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please email: info(at)bridging-the-gap(dot)com.

Updated: May 21, 2018
